(A Fated Meeting)
Nice to see you all.
- Nice to see you. - Oh, my.
Seriously. Our show is full of youthful faces, isn't it?
- Yes. - It's giving off a college vibe.
- What? - Stop it, Hyun Moo.
A college vibe...
That's why I dressed like a college student.
- For today's episode? - To look fresh.
- To look fresh. - Yes.
- That's your college student look? - Right.
(A fresh college student look)
I know I said "college student."
But I do look old. Like a soldier from the barracks, right?
Very much.
Considering the ranks,
Kian84's rank is the one to be feared the most.
- I'm the powerless sergeant. - He has the actual power.
- You'd have no real power. - I'd have no real power.
If you have a problem, talk to me first.
Okay. That sounds great.
Don't let Hyun Moo hear it.
- I'm a toothless tiger. - Right.
- Have we all met each other before? - No.
- Whom have you not met before? - It's my first time...
- meeting Dowoon today. - Really?
- We haven't met before. - Same here.
- MINHO is older. - We haven't met either.
- Right. - You two are the same age.
- Exactly. We're the same age. - Yes. You should be friends.
- Nice to meet you. - Yes.
Drop the honorifics since you're the same age.
You have to do what the powerful member says.
That's the rule.
- Right. You were both born in 1995. - That's right.
- You love fishing, Dowoon. - That's right.
I used to love fishing too.
Dowoon can catch fish.
Then Ji Hyeon can fillet them.
- That's right. - Yes.
- That's right. - Dowoon...
- Let's go fishing together. - Yes.
- Sounds good. I'd love to. - Yes.
Now, you guys have to lead the show.
- You must lead the show. - Right.
You guys have a lot to do.
That's because we're old news.
(We got it, sir!)
(Into the Winter)
"Into the Winter."
(Groaning)
(Current time, 5:20am)
That's way too early.
What's taking him so long?
It's the crack of dawn.
(What's he doing at Mount Cheonggye at the crack of dawn?)
It's freezing.
What's the temperature at?
It's at minus 10°C. Oh, my.
(Weather, minus 10°C)
But the apparent temperature is minus 11°C.
The temperature this morning dropped over 10°C...
- since yesterday. - It was the biggest cold wave.
The apparent temperature will go as low as minus 20°C.
- That's way too cold to be out. - Minus 20°C?
- It was really cold a few days ago. - Yes.
It wasn't as bad the day before.
Then it got extremely cold in the morning.
- Kian84. - Hey.
Hey, Dowoon.
It's Dowoon.
(He meets Dowoon early in the morning.)
- Did you sleep well? - What?
This year...
On the New Year's Day,
I didn't get to see the sunrise.
But I still wanted to see it in the beginning of the year.
I invited Dowoon of DAY6.
I decided to hike with Dowoon.
Surprisingly, at the bazaar,
all the items he chose were mine.
(This fishing rod looks great.)
You guys clicked well.
That's a cute boyfriend look.
(He connects especially well with Dowoon.)
We both like fishing.
We had a lot in common.
Exercising is the best way for guys to bond.
I wanted us to break a good sweat and get some exercise together.
I thought that always brought guys closer.
On top of that, he likes hiking too.
So we decided to go together.
Besides, Mount Cheonggye has good energy.
When I bought clothes from him,
he and I seemed to click well.
I thought, "This guy and I might get along well."
So I asked him to go hiking with me.
(Kian84 and Dowoon came to get good energy.)
- Did you get some sleep? - I only slept for three hours.
Let's go.
- Why didn't you invite me? - What?
That's the thing about me.
I can't interact with more than two people at once.
I can't multitask.
- Is he your new favorite now? - I wouldn't say that.
I can't talk to only one person at a time.
You might've been neglected had you come.
- I'll do better. - Gosh, no.
- Gosh, Ji Hyeon is so cute. - Oh, no.
- Kian84 is the leader. - What?
Is it my time now?
(Irresistible84 continues to draw attention from men.)
No, don't be disappointed. You two should be friends.
- Sounds good. - Sure.
(He begins hiking with his new guy.)
Do you go hiking often?
- Me? - Yes.
I sometimes go hiking.
I know that you do a lot of marathons.
- But these days, - Yes.
I run only 10km.
- Only 10km? - Yes.
Do you like staying active?
I keep exercising because I'm getting older.
I didn't exercise much when I was your age.
I was so full of energy then.
- How old are you? - I'm 32 years old now.
- You're 32? My gosh. - Yes.
That's why I exercise a lot now.
You must have so much energy now.
So you exercise a lot?
I box.
I need to be able to protect myself.
Ji Hyeon boxes too.
- You box too. - Yes.
He even participated in a boxing match.
- Really? - No, I didn't.
- You didn't? - When...
- You didn't? - I didn't.
- What? You need to be sure. - Ji Hyeon, do a match then.
- I thought you did five matches. - What are you talking about?
I even thought you won the match.
- What on earth? - How did the misinformation start?
- Right? - Are you planning to fight a match?
- No. I stopped boxing now. - I see.
- But you used to box? - Yes.
- Show him your jabs. - How many years...
I...
You're going to show us?
- He's going to show us? - Show us.
(His shadowboxing cuts through the air.)
(Impressed)
(Amazed)
It does feel like we're in the military, talking about this.
(A dull vibe)
This feels like reserve training.
When will you throw me a discharge party?
- Okay. We'll throw you a party. - I got the patches stitched.
Are you wearing the clothes you bought that day?
- The clothes look so cute. - Yes?
I'm not lying. I mean it. I actually wore it.
- Really? - I wore it 2 or 3 times.
Yes.
I've never hiked Mount Cheonggye at this hour.
- It's my 1st time. - It's my 1st time too.
It's my first time hiking Mount Cheonggye.
- Which way do we have to go? - We...
Yes.
We should go toward Maebong Peak. There.
- The elevation is about 580m. - That's quite high.
Kian84, do you often hike Mount Cheonggye?
That's the closest mountain from my place.
I go there at least 2 or 3 times a year.
- Maebong Peak looks great. - Okay.
It takes two hours.
(The Maebong Course takes 2 hours.)
The sun will rise before they reach the peak.
- It's 5:30am now. - It's 5:30am now.
Let me check the sunrise time.
Hey, the sun will rise at 7:40am.
- Really? It will be perfect then. - Yes.
- We have exactly 2 hours. - We have exactly 2 hours.
- We must hurry. - Let's go.
Yes.
- There's a slight incline. - What?
- There's a slight incline. - Yes.
Hey. This is nice, though.
- Isn't it nice? - I love it.
I can tell Dowoon is a positive, cheerful person.
(Hiking to the peak)
It's really dark.
It's dark. Let me turn on the lantern.
- People here... - Yes.
He brought a lantern.
There aren't any lamps.
Gosh, you can see my breath.
(Gosh, you can see my breath.)
Let's put on the climbing irons.
- I brought a pair for you too. - Thank you.
These are nice.
(Dowoon brought two pairs of climbing irons.)
Thank you for this.
- Are you all set? - Yes, I'm all set.
Without the lantern, you can't see anything.
It will be dangerous without climbing irons.
Gosh, it's a bit spooky here.
It's scary.
- It's a horror movie. - It's scary.
- Like we're walking into death. - Right. I thought so too.
(The two of them head into the pitch-black darkness.)
- Like we're walking into death. - It does feel like that.
Gosh, look how dark it is.
- It reminds me of "Mystery Squad." - Yes.
This is a scene straight out of "Gonjiam."
- My gosh. - Why is there a red light?
- Let's hurry. This is creepy. - This is so scary.
- That was sudden. - This is scary.
It was really creepy with the red light.
(Their hike gets spookier.)
You can't watch horror movies either?
Me? I can watch them with friends.
(I can't watch them alone.)
I don't like movies that are too extreme.
- But they're fun to watch. - Sure. But...
My gosh. Hello.
- What? - My goodness.
- Hello. - Who's that?
- I was so startled. - Seriously.
- It's like a Japanese horror movie. - What's this?
- Here's the thing. - I got so startled.
I couldn't see a thing. It was pitch-dark.
- She talked to us out of the blue. - Gosh.
- She was like, "Hey, Kian84." - Then...
- she must've started at 3am. - Exactly.
- She's going down now. - She's all alone too.
- She didn't have a lantern. - Right.
- That makes no sense. - She probably used her phone light.
- The flashlight from her phone. - Really?
It looked like she came for her morning prayer.
That's crazy.
That's so scary. My gosh.
- Hello. - She startled me.
I think Kian84 walked past her because he was scared.
- Right? - She was like, "What?"
I was flustered too.
- Safe hiking. - So we walked past each other.
I would've been startled too.
(The unexpected encounter flusters them both.)
- I... - At night...
I could never do this alone.
It looks like she's in special forces or something.
(It looks like she's in special forces or something.)
Gosh, why is it so long and scary?
- This is scary, right? - Right.
(Following the path the special agent must have walked)
You couldn't have hiked without the light.
Right. The lantern was a must.
- Let's go fishing sometime. - What?
- Let's go fishing sometime. - Yes, let's go fishing.
March or April?
March or April? Then there aren't a lot of boats on the west coast.
Do you want to fish in the freshwater?
- That sounds great. - I like freshwater fishing.
- Kian84, I... - My face won't be on TV, right?
Dowoon. It looks like you're up on stage.
- You have the lantern on your head. - Yes.
- His face won't be on TV today. - Right.
- It's like he's at a concert. - His face is really glowing.
- His face... - His handsome face is blinding me.
We've only heard of such a face.
- There's an incline. - What?
- There's an incline. - Yes.
(Panting)
They're getting tired.
(In no time, )
(only their sounds of breathing and footsteps are heard.)
Both of them started to get quiet.
You know how it feels.
I'd get annoyed when people talk to me then.
(Walking up)
Gosh, it's freezing.
(The temperature drops sharply as they hike up.)
You guys went on the coldest day.
Right. And at the coldest hour too.
My ears were about to freeze off.
Yes. It'd feel like they'd tear off.
(The current temperature, minus 14°C)
Aren't your ears cold?
- My ears? - Yes. Mine are about to freeze off.
Right.
I should've brought a hoodie.
- You're not wearing a hoodie. - Right.
Exactly. They didn't bring any proper gear.
- Right. - You should've worn earmuffs.
Seriously.
In my eyes, you two didn't dress properly for hiking.
I do admit that I treated the hiking trip lightly.
You thought it'd be easy like hiking a hill?
Yes, that's what I thought.
- I didn't know it'd be that cold. - It's tough.
- You'd also sweat on your way up. - Right.
You must wear several thin layers...
- of clothing. - Right.
If you only wear one padded jacket, it'd get too hot later.
- You'd be cold if you took it off. - Right.
That'd be uncomfortable.
- You should've covered your ears, - Right.
- your neck, and your hands. - Yes.
Covering up those places would have kept you warm.
(Their feet are beginning to get numb.)
(Looking flushed)
You look so cold, Kian84.
It looks like I drank two bottles of soju.
You look drunk.
- Even your eyes are out of focus. - Definitely.
(Looking drunk)
(His face gets puffy from the biting cold.)
I think we're halfway there.
(I think we're halfway there.)
- We can slow down. - Sure. Let's go. I can do it.
Let's go. I can do it.
Your body is going numb.
(Even his mouth is getting numb due to the cold.)
My gosh.
- Goodness. - Oh, my.
Darn it.
(In the end, his inner thought slips out.)
Gosh, why is it so high? We're not hiking the Himalayas.
The mountain must've gone up.
It's gotten taller.
(Exhausted)
It felt like I was getting punished then.
I kept feeling the burn in my legs.
Then there was nothing but darkness. I couldn't see a thing.
It was so cold. It was just painful.
- Right. - I bet.
If they were cold even when they were sweating,
it must've been extremely cold.
Actually, at that time, I kind of regretted deciding to hike.
- I regretted it. - Right.
- It was way too cold. - Yes.
- Was that the only time? - What?
- Never mind. - That was the only time.
- Really? - Yes.
- You're the type to hold grudges. - Gosh, no.
- That was the only time. - Really?
- Don't get the wrong idea. - Okay.
That's cute.
(Laughing)
(Panting)
(Glancing)
Hey, we're only 700m away.
They're amazing.
We've gotten far.
- Let's take a break. - Yes, let's take a break.
- Here. - Thank you.
(Sitting down to hydrate)
Drink some more.
(Slurring)
Gosh, the water tastes good.
(Dripping)
Water is dripping everywhere.
(Laughing)
You didn't feel the water dripping...
- because your mouth was numb. - Right.
The water actually felt warm.
Right.
(Of all days, )
(why are we hiking today?)
My gosh.
- Should we go? - Yes, it's getting cold.
- It's cold when we're not moving. - Yes. We need to keep moving.
- Once our body cooled down... - Yes.
- Right. We had to keep moving. - You'd get cold.
Your sweat would cool off.
(Panting)
My gosh. Seriously.
The sun is nowhere to be seen.
Right. I don't see the sun at all.
(Glancing back)
Dowoon, look over there. It's getting red.
This is cool.
(Dowoon, look over there.)
This is nice.
(The scenery of Seoul is seen as they climb higher.)
I'm starting to see Seoul now.
- It's like the view at the airport. - Yes.
- Before landing. - Right.
- It's the view from the plane. - Right?
- Yes. Right before landing. - The view at the airport.
That's a cool spot.
(Panting)
What? Are we here?
Hey, this is it.
(They're finally at the peak.)
We're at the peak.
(They make it to the peak at last.)
- You made it to Maebong Peak. - You made it.
We made it, but it was so dark.
Do you want a picture?
- Let's take one together. - Yes. Let's take it together.
Do you want to make a heart together?
Let's make one.
"Do you want to make a heart together?"
(They're serious about taking pictures even when it's cold.)
(Getting close)
- Did we get it? - Yes.
(Thanks for the good energy.)
Come on.
- This is scary. - It is.
We can't even tell you apart.
(Two unidentified hikers)
- By the way, - That couldn't have been easy.
I had never seen the peak being that empty.
- Right. - Seriously.
I went there 2 or 3 times. I had to line up to take a picture there.
This mountain gets a lot of hikers usually.
- Really? - Yes. It's a famous mountain.
Especially in spring.
(Current time, 6:55am)
Oh, no. This is bad. The sun won't rise for another 40 minutes.
(The sunrise time, 7:43am)
The sign said that it would take...
two hours to reach the peak.
Maybe, it was for a round trip.
Or maybe, we hiked quickly.
It turned out we got there only in an hour and a half.
We had to wait for 40 to 50 minutes until the sunrise.
We got there too early.
- Did you have to wait? - Yes.
We could've slept for one more hour.
You didn't get to look around while hiking.
- So anyone would've gone up fast. - Right.
You couldn't see anything around you.
- So... - I see.
- They just hiked up. - Yes.
- Dowoon, to see the sunrise, - Yes.
Let's go to Maebawi. Let's watch it from there.
- We can't see the sun from here. - It's because of the trees.
We'll get a better view there.
You can't go higher from there?
- No. - No. There's a rock...
only 100m away.
- Oh, there? - Yes.
Okay. I see. This was one of the peaks.
The view looks great from here.
(They can see a panoramic view of the city.)
There it is.
(Grabbing)
This helps us maintain our body temperature.
What's that?
- What is that? - Is it a hand warmer?
(What's that?)
- That's like silver foil. - Kian84. I brought this...
- in case we got cold. - It's the emergency silver foil.
It traps heat.
(Dowoon brought a survival item, a silver-foil blanket.)
- Like a sweatsuit? - Yes.
- Heat can't escape. - Right.
People wrap it around their body before the marathons.
- That's right. - They take it off when they start.
I doubt you packed it because you knew it'd be that cold.
I packed it just in case.
To be honest, I didn't think I'd use it.
I'm so glad you packed it. That saved you both.
I really didn't think I'd use it.
- Do you have one? Okay. Get it. - I'll take out mine.
(Shoving)
- What are you doing? - Why?
- My ears were way too cold. - I see. Your ears were cold.
Hey, this is warm.
Yes. It traps heat.
Hey, this is amazing.
- Really? - Yes.
- Is it good? - Yes.
I've never used it before.
- Gosh, this is great. - It looks pretty cold.
- But I guess it's not. - No.
- It's for insulation. - I can sit on my bag.
Gosh, it's freezing.
The sky has gotten brighter.
It's getting bright.
I don't think we can see the sun.
Are you sure we'll see the sun?
(Checking)
We need to wait for another 30 minutes.
(It's only 7:10am now.)
(Glancing)
This is the one.
(He takes another survival item from his backpack.)
- Here. - Oh, that?
- Yes. - Is it food?
- Oh, great. - My gosh.
You brought field ration. Gosh.
- Let's have one. - It tastes amazing.
- Of course. - He packed everything.
"Yukgaejang flavored ramyeon rice."
It heats up right away, right?
Yes.
- We just need to wait ten minutes. - Right.
- Gosh. - My goodness.
Hey.
I'm too cold to make it.
Hold on. Let me make it for you.
No. Give it to me. I'll do it.
Gosh, Kian84. Just sit tight.
(Look at this guy.)
How do you make this?
(Trying to take care of each other)
- You've never tried it, right? - No.
I've made that many times.
- "Then zip it up tightly." - Gosh.
(Grabbing)
- "Pour cold water..." - Hey, I'll do it.
- Kian84 is so cool. - "The ramyeon rice..."
Pour the water into this.
(The older guy prepares the field ration.)
- Is that all the water we have? - Yes.
- We don't have more water? - That's all we have.
- This is all the water we have? - That's it.
Hey, we can't make this then.
We drank everything.
(They drank up their precious water on their way up.)
- You drank a lot of water here. - Gosh, the water tastes good.
We need more water.
(Using every drop of the water)
- Let's try it. - Okay.
- I'll zip it. - Zip it.
- Gosh. - It's so cold.
My hands are about to freeze off.
(Their ears and hands might freeze off.)
- How many minutes? - It was way too cold.
- I couldn't keep my hands out. - Seriously.
Have some.
No, you should drink it. I'm okay.
I made it for you this morning.
- Really? Thank you. - Sure.
- Really? - Yes.
(Grateful)
Let's split that together.
Gosh, Kian84. It's hot. This is so good.
- Kian84, you should have some. - It's good, right?
- It must be nice to drink it there. - It was nice.
Job's Tears tea?
- It's coffee. - Coffee?
Your senses went numb.
- It was too cold to taste anything. - That's coffee?
- Right. Your tongue was numb. - It's coffee?
My tongue is numb.
My gosh. This is good.
My hands are so cold.
I'm afraid Kian84 might die at this rate.
Seriously.
We were tired too. It couldn't have gotten worse.
(His face is freezing in the cold.)
Kian84, wrap it around you.
You should wrap it around you.
I'll use mine.
No, I'll do it for you. Sit tight.
(The younger one puts a blanket around the older one.)
- Like this. - How sweet.
Yes.
(Desperately trying to block out the wind with the survival item)
(Shivering)
It must've been really cold.
(He makes sure Kian84 is okay first.)
- Here it is. My gosh. - This is really warm.
- Yes, Kian84. We need this. - This is really nice.
I'm so glad I packed these.
(Grateful)
- This feels nice. - Yes.
- You're wearing thin socks too. - Right.
Right.
(Exposed)
My gosh.
Look how red his ears are.
His lips got pale.
(Shaking)
You're still shaking even with the blanket?
It's really cold up there.
- He's not moving now. - Yes.
- Right. - It's colder with cool sweat.
It looks like we went there to pray.
(Two monks are sitting at the peak with fluttering blankets.)
If the blankets get reflected by the sun,
people will take pictures of you and think you're UFOs.
I wanted to come down.
(I wanted to give up on seeing the sunrise.)
I just thought that...
we wouldn't be able to last anymore.
It was the toughest moment.
(I want to be back in my warm house.)
It felt like minus 20°C.
- You should've covered your ears. - Right.
I couldn't feel anything.
When I touched my fingers, they felt like solid objects.
My senses were numb.
Right. Your senses would go numb.
The North Pole is much warmer.
Here's a message for those...
who are not sure whether or not to visit the North Pole.
The weather is about the same.
When I went up, I kept slurring my words.
I started to feel dizzy.
I don't even remember what we talked about.
Both of us look like beggars on the street.
- By the way, it must be ready now. - What?
That must be hot now.
Hey, this looks great.
(Steaming)
That looks so good.
- It looks amazing. - Yes.
- It's ramyeon rice. - It's ramyeon rice?
- Yes. - Rice.
- Dowoon. - Yes?
- Should I taste it first? - Go ahead.
- Okay. - Have some first.
- Then give me the bag. - Okay.
(Shaking)
Gosh, that looks great.
(Humming)
I want to know how it tastes.
- There's rice too. - Yes.
Right.
(Slurping)
(Inhaling the food without taking a breath)
- Thank you. - Here.
(Try a bite too.)
It's the best.
Gosh, it's so warm.
(Nice. It's warm.)
(Opening up his numb mouth)
Hold on.
I shouldn't laugh at this.
(Finding him cute)
(Enjoying it)
- Gosh. - Isn't it good?
Oh, my.
I didn't know he could change only in two hours.
The field ration is the best.
(Eating in a hurry)
Yes. Ramyeon after suffering like that...
- Yes. It tasted so different. - tastes different.
Kian84, put your hand on the bottom of the bag.
- It's warm. - Okay.
- It will warm up your hand. - Gosh, it's warm.
(Gosh, it's warm.)
(Slurping)
Kian84. Gosh, what are we? Beggars on the street?
(Sniffling)
I should try the soup too.
(Blowing)
(Thoroughly enjoying the warm soup)
Gosh, the soup...
I bet it tastes so good.
Dowoon, try the soup.
- The soup was great. - We had to take turns like that.
It'd be too cold to keep our hands out at the same time.
(Shaking)
- This is just crazy. - My gosh.
That's just pure misery.
Why did you guys go hiking that day?
Did you have to look at the sunrise that day?
You should've looked at it on another day.
- Another day? - You know?
You might be too busy eating and miss the sunrise.
Right?
Is the sun already up?
- Seriously. - Dowoon plays the drums.
His forearm muscles must be really strong.
It must've been really cold for his arms...
- to shake. You know? - Nothing can beat the cold waves.
Seriously.
(Thinking about it still gives him the chills.)
(It's nice to have warm ramyeon, though.)
(Finishing up)
Hold on. Let me bundle up.
(Wrapping himself)
- The sun will rise from there! - What?
I think it'll rise from there.
The sun rose! It already rose, right?
- You need to see the egg. - The egg?
- The yolk? - The white circle.
It's cloudy. They won't see it.
It's a bit nerve-racking, right?
I think the sun rose.
- That's... - I'll need to look it up.
(I'll need to look it up.)
It's the time of sunrise,
but because of those clouds...
I'll ask ChatGPT.
(Really?)
(AI84 is the best at utilizing AI.)
- Do you use it as well? - Of course.
I'm at Maebong, the summit of Mount Cheonggye...
right now.
Did the sun rise?
You went all the way up to Maebong, the summit of Mount Cheonggye.
You're curious about whether or not the sun rose, right?
It's around the time of sunrise.
Seeing the sun rise at the summit of a mountain...
will surely be nice.
Hey, we're asking if it rose!
I see. You want to know if it has risen already, right?
- I'm pretty sure... - Just answer without asking!
- The AI kept using flowery words. - I'm pretty sure it has risen.
- Give me that. - Okay.
When will we see the egg?
By my estimation, the clouds will part...
- in an hour or two... - In an hour or two,
- and you'll see the sun. - it'll be high up in the sky.
Will it take an hour or two?
Of course. If you wait...
(Stopping)
It doesn't know.
The AI technology isn't accurate yet.
I bet swear words are the data AI collects the most.
That's right.
- Is that the sun? - That's the sun.
If it goes up a bit more...
- I think the sun has risen. - It has risen.
It'll have to go up much further for us to see it.
It'll need to go up further, right?
(Let's see.)
Dowoon.
Let's just get rid of preconception...
that the sun is round!
- Exactly. - You see it, right?
(Let's just get rid of preconception that the sun is round!)
- It has risen. - Yes.
Shall we make a wish?
You can pray to Buddha and I can pray to the Almighty.
- Okay. Let's make a wish. - They're an optimistic duo.
- I love it. - Let's make a wish.
You guys are brighter than the sun.
It's cool.
- Amen! - Gosh, Buddha.
Homage to Amitabha Buddha.
(Homage to Amitabha Buddha.)
- We have different religions. - Religions.
They'll be confused about...
- They're so different. - whom to listen to.
I bet they're close up there.
Buddha will look after us.
That's right.
The Almighty will watch over us.
(Buddhism and Christianity are in one place.)
We prayed to our respective religious power.
I just wished...
that my parents would be healthy...
and that I'd be a good person to those around me.
I hoped that the round sun...
(Ta-da)
would come up like this.
But we did see the sun that was pretty round.
(Perhaps it was the sun of harmony.)
- Amen. - Amen.
Amen.
I ended up saying it.
- I got affected. - That was the vibe.
I always have this thought at the summit of a mountain.
"What was the use of all that squabbling in life?"
Up there, everything you see is the size of an ant.
It's like Buddhist TV.
I don't wish for something big.
I wish to continue being grateful for the things I have now.
Seriously,
I talk like my mom.
(Although their religions differ, they are of one mind.)
Amen.
(They fully charge the New Year energy.)
- Give it here. - Okay.
(They pick up the trash.)
- Let's go. - The sun has risen.
What's wrong with my hair? I need to get a haircut.
(Let's smile.)
I look so ugly!
Both of you look like you went through a lot.
Did you use an app?
Please Photoshop it.
I climbed Mount Halla, right?
Hiking makes you look old.
You look much older.
Seriously.
The sun rose in the end.
The sun rose. Hey, I'm glad I came here.
(They braved coldness for four and a half hours to see the sun.)
- It's pretty. - Yes.
Let's go.
- My feet are numb. - Yes.
- You did well, Kian84. - You did well.
(They fully recharged their energy.)
It's much warmer than earlier.
(They get into Dowoon's car.)
- I'll drive slowly. - Thank you.
(Kiwoon Duo heads somewhere.)
What will you do this year? Will you have concerts?
We'll have concerts this year.
Do you go to Japan often?
Japanese people like bands.
- You're right. - Yes.
I absolutely loved X Japan back in the day.
I've heard of X Japan.
(X Japan was a band that represented Japan in the 90s.)
They were the best.
I wanted to get that hairstyle.
I wanted to get that hairstyle too.
"Endless Rain."
(His eyes become teary as he reminisces about the past.)
What were some other songs? "Tears."
I like old songs too.
Back in the days,
I listened to death metal.
It goes like...
(They reach the suburbs as they share their musical tastes.)
Do you perform in Japan the most after Korea?
That's right. We perform in Japan a lot.
I'll need to learn Japanese from you.
Let's speak Japanese until we arrive.
Okay.
Because...
of animation...
(Blinking)
I use animation...
- to... - Okay.
Studying...
To study?
"To study?"
(To study?)
I can babble...
for a bit.
"For a bit."
- But... - Hey.
- Why isn't your Japanese improving? - What?
- It isn't improving at all. - What?
- Association takes a while. - Association.
(He began studying Japanese 6 months ago.)
(He used associative technique to memorize the words.)
(A monkey is flippant, so it'll be at "Saru," the 4th base.)
(Thus, monkey is "Saru" in Japanese.)
While you remember,
- putting them together takes time. - Association takes time.
- "For a bit." - But...
How do you say "To listen?"
Say it in Korean then.
"To listen." This isn't good.
This isn't good.
Japanese in animation is different.
- That's right. How should I say it? - Different.
It's a bit violent.
- What was that? - Violent.
- Violent? - Yes.
Violent.
The way you said it...
- It has the gangster vibe. - Yes.
"Who do you think you are? Let's do this."
They shouldn't talk like that. It's too tough.
"Who is this punk?"
"Move!"
My Japanese is a bit tough.
"Who is this punk? For goodness' sake."
It's like picking a fight...
- with Japanese people. - That's right.
"One Piece," "Bleach," "Naruto..."
There are hundreds of episodes.
I've watched them for ten years.
"What are you looking at, you punk?"
- "What is it, you fool?" - "What is it?"
- "You fool." - It's like that.
I have a Japanese teacher.
- Is that so? - Yes.
I pay...
- You pay. - I pay.
My mom...
Your mom.
Is your mom Japanese?
(Is your mom Japanese?)
Did you ask if his mom was Japanese?
Is your mom Japanese?
Not at all.
My mom is Korean.
Korean.
(I'm sorry.)
But my mom...
likes Japanese culture.
- Japanese culture. - Yes.
It's "Bunka."
(They stop at the traffic signal.)
This is where we stop due to the signal.
(He's full of confidence when he knows the word.)
I love it.
He's like a character from an animated series.
You...
aren't very...
- Very... - "Good?"
You aren't very good at Japanese.
Thank you.
Hey, why are you thanking him for saying that you're bad at it?
(Kiwoon Duo communicates through energy, not words.)
I see. I misunderstood.
But he's definitely better than me.
- I learned a lot. - Why would you even compare?
- We're about the same. - I learned a lot.
Because you have an accent as a dialect user,
- That's right. - you'll sound fluent...
if you learn the language a bit more.
Busan residents are good at Japanese.
- That's right. - That's right.
- Why is that? - The accent is similar.
- The accent? - Yes.
Back in the day,
I went to an izakaya in Gimhae, a city near Busan.
The owner was like, "What brings you all the way here?"
I thought he was speaking Japanese.
I thought that was the concept.
- "What are you going to eat?" - I thought it was Japanese.
- You were at an izakaya. - Yes.
"What are you going to order?"
- You're good. - Thank you.
Gosh,
you speak two languages.
I find Korean hard too.
Korean? It's hard.
I don't know the difference between "Dwae" and "Doe."
- "Dwae" and "Doe?" - Yes.
I'll teach you. It's easy.
- I'll set things straight. - Dozens of people...
have taught me so far.
I'll put an end to it.
- Do you know how I know? - He's an artist.
I published webcomics for ten years, right?
- I made many spelling mistakes, - That's right.
- so I learned. - I see.
There's a Grammar of the Year Award for the Naver webcomics artists.
I won it for eight years.
It's given to the webcomics artist...
who has made the most number of grammatical mistakes.
Really? What a twist.
Seriously.
- It isn't a good award. - I didn't know about that.
- It encourages you to improve. - I see.
Grammar.
(Grammatical errors)
I got many grammar lessons from them.
So I can teach people that much.
Here's the difference between "Dwae" and "Doe."
Associate them...
with "Hae" and "Ha."
"Hey, why did you become that way?"
Change "Dwae" to "Hae."
- "Why did you do that?" - "Why did you do that?"
It makes sense, so it's "Ae."
- "Ae." - If you use "Ha..."
Then it doesn't make sense.
So...
it isn't "Ha."
Am I explaining it in a difficult way?
I never had a problem with that,
but I think I'll get confused starting today.
Your Korean is worse than your Japanese.
I wanted to explain it in an easy way.
If using "Hae" makes sense,
- it should be "Dwae." - That's right.
"I shouldn't do that."
- "I won't do that." - That's right.
If using "Ha" makes sense, it should be one line.
- For "Ha," it's 1 line. - It's 1 line.
- "Ha." Okay. - Yes.
I get it.
I explained it for so long. But Hyun Moo did it...
- He said the same thing. - Yes.
- That's right. - You complicated it so much.
- I have a question. - Okay.
For "To pester," I don't know...
- if I should use "Dae" or "Doe." - Okay.
- Which one should I use? - It's "Dae."
- "Dae." - It's "Ae."
That's one word.
- That's right. - The same rule doesn't apply.
- You're similar to us. - "Dae."
I knew the "Ha" and "Hae" trick.
- I... - He drew the line...
- right away. - Seriously. I knew that much.
Okay.
Let's say you go,
"Give me food!"
- "Is the food ready?" - "Is the food ready?"
"Did you make food?"
- "Hae." - It's "Ae."
That's right.
No. Since it's "Hae..."
You're right. It's "Ae."
Correct.
- What's this? - That's right.
- Yes. - You understood, right?
(As they exchange their language skills, )
(they arrive at a place.)
Where are they going?
- I think I'll pass out. - It's another mountain.
I think it's a rest area.
(The place they are going to)
- It's a sauna. - A sauna?
- A fire dome sauna. - It's perfect.
I went to a fire dome sauna once.
It's great.
(Charcoal-fueled fire dome sauna)
I'm so jealous, I love saunas.
I went to a sauna today.
It's amazing when the weather is cold.
It was a good memory.
Since the weather was cold,
I thought it'd be nice for us to go together.
- That was how we ended up going. - It's the perfect course.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
- Two people, please. - Okay.
(Taking out the card)
Hey!
- Kian84. - Hey!
- Let's pay separately. - Hey!
(Gosh, Kian84)
You can pay for the entrance fee with your card.
Inside, you can pay with this key.
He often pays for people who are younger than him.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- Take your key. - Okay.
Use the men's changing room. Put on your socks...
- and go out through that door. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(They change right away.)
You're right.
It's chilly.
(They change into the sauna clothes and enter.)
My goodness.
- People... - Let's buy sikhye.
Hello.
- Let's drink sikhye. - Two sikhye.
Sikhye looks tasty.
Here you go.
(Handing over the key quickly)
Thank you.
Why do you keep paying?
Don't pay at the cafeteria.
- Okay. - Let me pay here.
Okay.
He said that after Dowoon paid.
Kian84 gets angry if you pay for something cheap.
- I get it now. - He wants to pay for that.
- He said that after Dowoon paid. - He wants to brag.
- This must be the place. - I know.
(Excuse me.)
- It's cold. - It's cold.
I see. It's open.
It's outdoors.
What? Is it outdoors?
- Is it outdoors? - It's outdoors.
- I've never seen such a place. - It looks nice.
Sweet potatoes are delicious there.
It's outdoors.
(Fascinated)
Which room will be nice?
- It's cold. - There are different rooms.
Medicinal Room.
(When you enter the fire dome)
- It's a fire. - Yes.
It's the best.
(Since the fire is hot, they sit down facing the wall.)
Am I doing this right?
- Gosh, it's hot. - It was so hot.
It was my first time at a sauna like that. It was fascinating.
(They begin to enjoy the sauna in earnest.)
Oh, my.
It's hot.
Seriously.
It's nice.
- I had to heat up the front. - Yes.
I can see that Kian84 is experienced.
(Glancing over)
(Shall I turn around as well?)
(The fire dome sauna newbie copies Kian84.)
I'll copy you.
(He puts a towel over his face like Kian84.)
Being experienced, Kian84...
- covered his face with a towel. - Yes.
(I'm practically melting.)
(Sweat rolls down.)
(Licking)
Wait.
- I guess it was tasty. - It was salty.
Gosh, right now...
Look at that sweat.
Sweat is rolling down my face.
They must be drowsy.
(Drowsy)
(They were shaking in the cold only a few hours ago.)
Earlier...
(They escaped the mountain where they shook in the cold.)
This is great.
(They enjoy the hot fire dome therapy.)
It was a great idea to go to a sauna after hiking.
That's right.
(Laughing)
This is amazing.
(The newbie is satisfied.)
After coming down from the mountain,
a sauna is great for recovery.
- Recovery. That's right. - Recovery.
I wanted to say that, but I couldn't remember the word.
It isn't a difficult word.
He doesn't disappoint.
(Gaining knowledge)
Let's go.
Gosh, this is...
I sweated so much.
(They head out after sweating.)
It's cool.
Your back is soaked.
- I can feel the cold air. - Right?
- You feel it when you step out. - Yes.
(They enter the next room.)
- Yes. - It's Kian84.
- It's him. - Let's shake hands.
Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year. - I'll receive energy from you.
He's very good at running a marathon.
- That's right. - Yes.
- I went hiking with a friend today. - Really?
We're pretty good at running too.
- Did you run a full marathon? - Of course.
Really?
- We did that. - That's impressive.
I watched you cook the seaweed soup.
Your mom is cool.
- Your mom. - Really?
I didn't know that.
She watches all the shows.
She was like my aunt.
She knew everything.
I'm only interested in Kian84.
(I know Kian84 well because I like him.)
It was a nice sight.
He was the prince among the elderly citizens.
I could feel that the elderly citizens...
cherished him and loved him a lot.
They liked him a lot.
Watching them made me feel good.
I see.
You resemble my eldest son a lot.
- Really? Your eldest son? - Yes.
When he began going out with his current girlfriend,
she told him that she liked him because he resembled Kian84.
- Because he resembled me? - Yes, she said that.
She saw his heart.
Am I dreaming?
Why do I keep hearing these words?
(Even his mind is recovering.)
Shall we go and eat?
- Let's go. - Okay.
My sweat is bursting out.
Have a fun time. I don't know what to say.
Have a nice day.
- "Enjoy the sauna." - "Enjoy the sauna."
Take care, ma'am.
Gosh.
- It's hot. - I know.
What do they sell?
(They go to the 2nd floor where the restaurant is located.)
Two portions of pork belly,
- one bowl of doenjang jjigae, - Right.
- and a bowl of mukbap, please. - Mukbap sounds delicious.
(Taking a look)
- Both of our clothes are a mess. - What?
- Our clothes are a mess. - I sweated so much.
Didn't you wet yourself?
- It's especially wet right there. - I sweat a lot.
- I sweated a lot as well. - Why is the sweat coming out here?
Gosh.
It doesn't matter where it comes out as long as it comes out.
- I feel drowsy. - Right.
After all this sweating.
I feel drowsy.
(They loosen up after going through a big temperature difference.)
- Here's the pork belly. - Thank you.
- Enjoy your meal. - Thank you.
This was placed in there?
(The pork belly was cooked in advance.)
It's a work of art.
That would taste amazing.
(The doenjang jjigae gets served next.)
- Mukbap. - It looks great.
(Picking up)
- Do you like onions? - Yes. Fresh ones.
- You can have it cooked. - I don't eat onions.
- You don't eat onions? - I don't.
Gosh, you're still young.
- Onions taste so good. - What does that have to do...
with being young?
I didn't eat onions at his age as well.
(Crunchy)
(He eats the fresh onion like an apple.)
(Fascinated)
It looks cooked. I think we can eat it now.
- Right. - Let's dig in.
- Right. Let's dig in, Kian84. - Right.
Is it eaten like this?
(He makes a big wrap with the pork belly.)
Like this?
Gosh, I feel hungry.
(He eats the pork belly first just like Kian84.)
(Satisfied)
It's good.
Gosh, check out the mukbap.
Gosh, that's a combination that can never go bad.
Mukbap is great.
- Is it good? - Give it a try.
Any place I go to has great food.
I usually don't eat a lot,
but I finished everything there as it tasted so good.
- You ate well that day. - Right.
Do you not usually meet up with your younger friends?
Younger friends?
Just in general. Are you usually with older friends?
Yes. I like being with older friends.
- Really? - Yes.
I feel comfortable being with younger friends.
Really?
I feel comfortable being with older friends.
(Smiling)
(He picks up a spoonful of the doenjang jjigae with a smile.)
That looks really good.
Gosh, this is great.
Gosh, it's refreshing.
I'm full.
We finished everything.
(Chewing)
(Is Dowoon still chewing?)
Jjondeugi?
Hey, you should grill it.
You have to grill jjondeugi.
- You can't eat it like that. - Why not?
Should I grill it some more?
It's not that. It touched the charcoal.
It's fine.
(Charcoal-grill in contact)
- "In contact." - It's just wood anyway.
- What? - It's fine.
Gosh.
I'm seeing this live.
The jjondeugi tastes good.
- Right. - Let's grill another piece.
Here you go.
I came because I wanted to sit next to you, Kian84.
- That's fine with me. - Let's shake hands.
Right. Happy New Year.
- Let's shake hands. - Right.
(That's my friend.)
Gosh, the ladies love you.
- I just watched the rerun. - Right.
You should also greet them.
- He looks handsome, doesn't he? - Right.
Gosh.
- He's good-looking. - Right.
He's a musician. He's in a band.
He's in a Korean Wave band.
- Not at all. - A Korean Wave band.
Not at all.
I think Kian84's charm is the sense of comfort.
Nothing felt uncomfortable between us.
We both respected each other.
He kept asking me the things he was curious about me.
That made things feel comfortable.
I enjoyed every moment I spent with Kian84.
I feel comfortable being with younger friends.
He treats older friends well.
I think that was how we clicked.
(The members of the Kiwoon Duo are a great match.)
- Gosh. - Gosh, you even have great looks.
Gosh, you're flattering me!
(Acting cute just like Kian84)
Isn't he good-looking? Right.
(Our Friendship Burns Brightly)
(I Live Alone)
(Busy Bread)
- "Busy Bread." - "Busy Bread."
It's always about bread with him.
Let's go!
(Bum June and Monde are out for a walk early in the morning.)
- Gosh, it's your baby! - Right.
Let's go!
Hello.
I'm Actor Seo Bum June. It's a pleasure to meet you!
(A bite of bread...)
(fills him up with joy.)
(With his love for bread throughout all three meals, )
(his freezer...)
(turned into a bread freezer.)
(He's a true bread lover.)
He really enjoys the bread.
Right. He made it look so good.
What surprised me...
was that there were a lot more bread lovers than I thought.
A lot of people contacted me...
and said they didn't know that I was a big bread lover.
The owners of bakeries seemed really happy to see me.
(He's heading somewhere with Monde today.)
- Where are you going this early? - We're here.
We're here, Monde.
(What is this smell?)
(He arrived somewhere early in the morning.)
Hello.
- Gosh, it's bread again. - Of course.
(Croissants that are crispy outside and soft inside)
- They're glossy. - I heard that it tasted good...
when made early in the morning.
Right.
- Dubai? - Oh, that?
That's so good.
- That is a big trend these days. - Dubai.
- Dubai chocolate. - It's past DCC now?
- There are Dubai croissants now? - Yes.
Dubai croissants?
You know DCC, right?
- I don't. - It's really popular these days.
- Have you tried it? - I have.
- How was it? - It was really good.
- I'm a true Gen MZer. - Really?
(Thinking)
Did you hear about this?
Even at Chinese restaurants or seafood restaurants,
the most popular dish is DCC.
Right.
Oh, the bread served in Chinese restaurants?
- No. - No.
Those are the flower buns!
DCC...
- is made with marshmallow skin. - Marshmallow skin.
The pistachio spread...
- and kadayif are mixed together. - They're mixed together.
- There's something like that? - Kian84.
DCC is Dubai chewy cookies.
- Dubai chewy cookies? - Chewy cookies.
Why shorten it like that?
It's because it sounds too long.
A lot of people make it on their own these days.
- Right. - I'm going to try making some.
Please bring down its popularity.
- Please bring it down. - Well,
I get a lot of DMs.
Since DCC is so popular,
people want me to make it myself.
- It's to bring down its popularity. - Well...
It'll be over soon.
Let's show everyone what you can do.
- I'll try making MCC. - Sounds good.
I'll make it myself and bring down its popularity.
- Okay. - So you all can enjoy it easily.
- Yes! - Yes!
I can finally have some now!
Do you have Dubai croissants?
Yes.
(Oh, my gosh!)
- I'll have three Dubai croissants, - Right.
One strawberry and cream croissant,
one egg tart,
one Nuneddine, and one alligator pie.
Gosh, I want some now.
Gosh, they look delicious.
- Thank you. Bye! - Bye!
Let's go!
(He returns home with Monde in his arms.)
- Gosh, it's 8am. - It's 8am?
Gosh, you hate it, don't you? My baby!
(Let's wipe your paws since you went for a walk.)
Let's wipe your muzzle as well.
- Monde is so gentle. - He's adorable!
Right.
- How adorable! - Let's comb your muzzle.
- Here. - He's an adorable dog.
You look great.
(Feeling clean)
Monde.
Shall we eat?
Dogs understand that line so well.
- Right. - You're so excited!
(Spinning)
Come here, Monde.
(Pouring)
Go ahead and eat.
(Digging in)
(Now that I have fed Monde, )
(shall I eat as well?)
I finally got my hands on the Dubai croissant, Monde.
Do you want some?
Gosh, a croissant with Dubai chocolate must be so good.
That must be really good.
- That looks good. - It's amazing!
(He reverently pulls up his sleeves first.)
(He picks up the large Dubai croissant.)
(Exclaiming)
That's the best moment for me.
- So that's in trend these days. - Right.
(Fully focused)
(Gasping)
- Gosh. - It's completely filled.
It really is completely filled up.
(Focused)
The sound when eating that...
- Right. - is the highlight.
(Crunch)
- It's like an ASMR video. - It sounds amazing.
Gosh, that must be so good.
(Jealous)
(Amazed)
(What is this crunchiness?)
(Sipping)
This person is well-educated. White milk!
- Of course! - Without a doubt.
Low-fat milk.
(He takes another big crunchy bite.)
My gosh!
Did you hear the sound?
I did.
(His hands drop down.)
(A taste that makes him go weak just thinking about it)
It doesn't make sense. It's so good.
The savory flavor kicks in right away.
I said I heard you as if you were a cult leader.
"I did!"
The Dubai cult.
(This time, he tries just the Dubai filling.)
(Smiling)
He really makes it look good.
This was possible because he was...
- diligent, right? - Yes.
- They all get sold out. - Right.
Right. An opening rush is a must.
(This is why I make opening rushes.)
- There's a reason this sells out. - Already?
- That tastes good as well. - Gosh, it must be so good.
(He isn't fully satisfied.)
He's having another one?
(The bread lover goes wild.)
- That's the Nuneddine croissant. - That looks great as well.
That alligator pie!
- It's called the alligator pie? - Alligator.
- Alligator? - Yes.
It's called the alligator pie?
- Alligator? - Alligator?
Yes. That was amazing.
Is it called that because it looks like the back of one?
Right.
The top of the croissant is coated with sugar.
There are pecans placed in between.
That's why it's completely crunchy.
That must be delicious.
I'll just get changed.
(He dresses up again after eating the bread.)
I'll be back, Monde!
(He leaves the house for the 2nd time at 9am.)
This person is truly amazing.
Let's get going.
(A good girl inside)
Old songs are great.
I love songs from 2010.
They're great.
- That was the golden era... - Right.
- of K-pop. - Right.
(He drives while listening to songs of the K-pop golden era.)
I'm late.
You must be heading to an important appointment.
Right.
(Where is he going?)
It's where I did my Fun Run!
That darn Fun Run? I'm so sick of it!
(Is he doing a Fun Run just like Gen MZer Moomoo?)
Fun Run!
I'm here.
(Packed)
- What is that? - Where is he going?
- He has a bag as well. - He's carrying a bag.
(He starts walking toward his destination.)
(Rushing)
(He starts running all of a sudden?)
Here it is!
(It's 10:10am.)
(Bum June arrives somewhere after driving early in the morning.)
(Startled)
Actually, I'm on a bakery pilgrimage trail today.
(Actually, I'm on a bakery pilgrimage trail today.)
Really?
I can't live without bread.
The Bread Freak.
I love bread as well.
- Daejeon, - Sungsimdang.
- Sungsimdang. - Busan,
- People go to Busan as well. - and Daegu.
I've been to Gangneung as well...
for a bakery pilgrimage trail. I've been to many places.
This time, I'll be in Seoul.
Yeonnam, Mangwon, Seongsu,
Gangnam, Apgujeong, Jamsil,
and Songnidan-gil. I've been to many places.
So this time, I'll be visiting Seochon.
Seochon!
- Don't you know that area? - There are so many great places.
I've done a lot of planning for the bakery pilgrimage trail.
I've made a list of the bakeries I wanted to visit.
It's so detailed.
- It's like he's taking an exam. - That's what I do.
I checked the locations and the places I wanted to visit...
to come up with a list.
That was how I chose the places for today.
Actually, I chose around 30 places...
I wanted to visit in Seochon.
He wrote down what he must have at each place.
- Right. - You also have to know...
when the bread gets made.
- Right. - That's important.
- We should go on a tour together. - He planned everything.
- I've never made a plan for food. - I plan everything thoroughly.
- Same here. - I'm all in for it.
(He visits the first place with an excited heart.)
(Startled)
What is this place?
Originally, you have to wait in line...
- for around two hours. - In line?
But I went on a weekday and I didn't have to wait.
- Gosh. - It was such a relief!
I'm finally here.
He looks genuinely excited.
What's surprising is that he just had bread in the morning.
- He's a man crazy about bread. - He's a man crazy about bread.
- Hello. - Hello.
I'll get a jalapeno melting cheese sandwich...
and an iced Americano.
Right.
(He walks up to the upper floor without finding a seat.)
They sell bread on the second floor.
The first floor is for sandwiches and other meals.
(He scans through the various types of bread.)
- I feel hungry all of a sudden. - I'll get that.
- I'll make an order, sir. - Sure.
I'll get one olive cheese campagne,
one corn cheese jalapeno campagne,
- That looks good. - It's nice and salty.
- Campagne? - and one blue cheese baguette.
- Campagne. - I'll get those three.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(He returns to his seat to eat.)
(While waiting for his sandwich...)
I'll go there next.
(He meticulously checks for the next place on the tour.)
Right.
(The sandwich is finally out.)
Here's the jalapeno melting cheese sandwich.
Thank you.
I really wanted to try this.
(He finally encounters the jalapeno melting cheese sandwich.)
(The melt cheese drizzles down.)
- There's steam coming out. - I love cheese.
Right? I love cheese and butter.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
There's the jalapeno.
(He feels touched.)
(Astonished)
- Awesome! - Gosh, that's amazing.
That's insane! Gosh!
I love cheese.
Awesome!
That looks so good!
(Smiling)
He looks so happy.
It was incredible.
- That must be good. - That looks so good.
Gosh.
I highly recommend that one.
That must be eaten there.
(He blows on the warm cheese.)
(This is the bite he has been waiting for.)
(Stretching out)
It's stretching out.
Gosh.
(Gosh, would you take a look at this piece of bread?)
(Looking carefully)
- What is this? - I'm so hungry right now.
(You can't be this good.)
Why at this hour? It's driving me crazy!
(This is it.)
The cheesy taste must be controlled with the jalapeno.
- Right. - Exactly.
The ciabatta has a clean taste.
The yellow cheese is mixed together with the mozzarella.
Say that while looking at Kian84.
(I see.)
(Not interested)
- Gosh, Kian84! - He's not interested.
(A world that Kian84 cannot understand at all)
But you can also taste the apple compote in between.
That's when you feel a sweet taste.
- It's a perfect harmony then. - It's perfect.
- It's perfect. - It's a triple beat...
with its sweet, salty, and spicy tastes.
- I can't imagine what it's like. - That must be so good.
All that running was worth it.
(Taking a bite)
He has a big mouth as well.
- He really enjoys eating bread. - Right.
It looks even better because he eats slowly.
It looks like he's actually tasting the food.
He's not just shoving it down his throat.
(Turning his head)
- Why are you looking at him? - Why are you looking at me?
- No! Don't get me wrong! - Hey!
Do I just shove things down my throat?
- You enjoy food the best. - So you do taste the food.
But it does seem like you shove in the food.
- That looks so good! - My gosh.
(He takes the last bite while enjoying the taste.)
This is what happiness is.
Right. Happiness is right by us.
Right.
Bye.
Thank you.
(He heads outside after being filled with joy.)
Why does the world seem brighter?
My gosh.
(The world looks beautiful for Bread June after eating bread.)
Let's see.
(The Bread Tour continues.)
This is the perfect course!
But when you feel full,
doesn't it bring down the desire of wanting to go somewhere?
- No. I don't feel full with bread. - Right.
- Each place feels different. - Right.
My gosh. He's going into another place.
The bread smells amazing.
(The second place is a bread master's place.)
It's a master's place.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Jaw-dropping)
(The place you can see when you walk out from the first place)
Right, a place like that...
- Do you know that place? - Yes. It's Hyoja.
It's famous.
I don't think you can go there.
- Why not? - Because it means "good son."
(The bad son can only cry.)
(Only good sons should go there.)
Hyun Moo can't go there.
I guess I can't go there to follow the trend.
You need to go after the trend dies.
(He enters the bakery where bad son Moomoo can't go.)
No way.
Gosh, the smell of the bread is...
You know how a bakery like that has a different smell of bread?
Yes, I do.
I do. It has the smell imbued with history.
Their breads are very Korean.
Like mammoth bread.
- It'll come out warm. - The corn bread?
Yes. Have a good day!
- That corn bread. - What is that?
(Gulping)
Can I just grab this?
- I'll put it in for you. - Thank you.
(Straight into the cart as soon as he sees it)
- Here you go. Sure. - Thank you.
Gosh, when you smell the freshly baked bread...
(Gulping)
(Naturally grabbing another bread)
(Halting)
What do I do? I can't get all of these.
(But he gently places it on the tray.)
I can't help myself. Goodness.
(His head says no, but his hands won't stop.)
- I'll take these. - That's it?
Yes.
- Thank you. - Keep it open on the way.
- Okay. - Close it when it cools down.
- All right. Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you so much.
(He filled his bag more fully with bread at the second place.)
Thank you!
I get why he brought his bag.
He doesn't know...
- when he'll visit again. - That's right.
- Since he's there... - He has to stock up...
- when he makes the trip. - That's it.
- What is it? - Is he going to smell it?
- He's eating one. - No, he has to eat one.
- He's eating one. - Of course. He has to.
How can you hold back?
(Taking a bite)
You call it EWW.
Eating the freshly baked bread. Eating while walking.
Eating while walking.
You should taste the freshly baked bread...
before it's put into the freezer.
(Quickly taking a bite while it's still warm)
I can even eat it with my gums only.
That'd be really uncomfortable.
There's onion and pepper in it.
The kick that pepper gives...
The pepper gives a kick between the soft bread.
- I should visit there to try it. - Yes.
- I should go too. - I'll take you guys.
- We should... - I think we should really go.
- Let's really go one day. - Let's go.
- We should really go. - Seriously. The bread...
- I think two of them won't go. - I'll go there.
Let's go by ourselves.
- Excluding these two? - Kian84.
Kian84, let's just have gukbap.
Let's just have pork gukbap.
(Bum June is highly satisfied with the bread.)
You're having a croquette too?
- That looks really good. - I prefer this.
- Me too. I prefer it too. - I prefer this.
(Crunchy)
Gosh, I'm really starving.
Did you see the batter?
- The crumbs... - The crumbs...
It's like a hedgehog.
It leaves your mouth chafed.
- You're eating one again? - He's having another one.
(The fourth place he came to to eat again)
(It's the Hong Kong bread place.)
- What's Hong Kong bread? - It's a pineapple bun.
Pineapple bread?
You can choose...
different kinds of butter and put it in between.
Isigny Butter, Echire Butter, Gourmet Butter.
- Oh, even Echire Butter? - Or President Butter.
You can choose one.
- They have different flavors. - That's right.
So that day, I got Isigny Butter and Echire Butter...
and put it in between.
Bum June, I'm learning a lot from you.
- I know. Seriously. - Seriously...
I really wanted to try it when I was in Hong Kong,
but I couldn't.
You can get it in Seochon.
(Jealous)
(Taking a big bite)
(A bakery pilgrimage trail where he savors butter properly)
I guess the bakeries are within walking distance.
Yes, I planned a route like that.
Oh, on purpose?
I find people who do a bakery pilgrimage amazing...
because you need to have fish cake soup in between.
I can't have all that because it's too choking.
Like a bowl of bean sprout gukbap we had during Grand Rainbow Bazaar.
Exactly!
One with crab.
- A sip of fish cake soup! - That sounds good.
You need to have...
- a cup of that before moving on. - By the way,
what was that? "Exactly!"
- I said that? - "Exactly!"
(Super excited at the thought of having fish cake soup)
I'd never heard that tone from you.
(Buzzing)
How pretty!
Hello.
Thank you.
(The ladies notice Bum June.)
You were recently in that drama. What's it called again?
- "Would You Marry Me?" - Yes.
I really enjoyed it.
I hated your character.
- Please give me your autograph. - Gosh, of course.
You can't even walk around the streets anymore.
So many people recognize me thanks to the drama.
- Ms. Hye Sook. - I'm really grateful.
You were annoying.
(His acting was really annoying.)
- You were really annoying. - Right.
- Become a superstar. - Thank you.
I'll work hard and show an even better performance.
Of course. I'm sure you'll be in a lot of dramas.
Let's shake hands. I hope you'll make it.
Ma'am, this is...
I just bought these.
- The croquette is really good. - Oh, my. How sweet of him.
- So I... - No, it's okay.
- No, you can have it. - You did well.
We'll buy it ourselves.
She said, "No." And he's going, "Have it."
The fact that he gave bread when he loves it so much...
means he was grateful toward the ladies.
- It's like he gave his everything. - He gave everything.
I don't know how to act like that.
I should learn to do it.
You've been saying that...
- for ten years. - I only know how to accept.
I've been hearing you say that for ten years.
- You're so pretty. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Happy New Year.
(Star Bum June's heartwarming fan meet-and-greet)
- Mothers love croquettes. - Thank you.
- Right. Mothers love croquettes. - Happy New Year.
For sure.
All right.
He's going to another one?
Oh, it's here.
There must be a lot of places you want to visit around the world...
- because of bread. - That's true.
- Right? - Yes.
- Because I love bread... - If you go to Europe...
Hello.
(He's happy when he's just looking at bread.)
Pistachio chocolate croissant...
- I'll take three of that. - Yes.
Two kouign-amanns, two pain suisse,
- and one Paris-brest. - I've tried a kouign-amann.
- It's really good, right? - And one apple pie.
- Isn't it a round one with sugar? - That's right.
Except for apple pie, it's my first time hearing them.
It's my first time hearing all of them.
Yes.
(Buzzing)
(Glancing)
You can take a photo with me.
- Oh, you went there. - It was right there.
We came for the bakery pilgrimage.
- Bakery pilgrimage? - No way.
- They must be pilgrims. - Yes.
Pilgrims meet each other.
We came here from Daegu.
From Daegu?
Where are you visiting today?
We went to M bakery,
- and we went to S bakery. - Oh, my.
- Then we came here. - Oh, my.
They went to the same places I went to.
We're going to the bakery that Chef Park Joon Woo runs.
The one that opens at noon?
(I know that place.)
Oh, my.
Just hearing that...
It's my first time seeing a world like that.
I really wanted to go.
So there's a community like that.
- I didn't know it existed. - The line was too long.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
This is so much fun.
Would you...
- You bought a lot. - What?
Try this.
- What? - Can we really?
- Yes. - What?
One has Isigny Butter, and the other one has Echire Butter.
They must be really happy.
The pilgrims have met each other.
- Try it. It's good. - It's my birthday today.
I feel like I was given a birthday gift.
- It's your birthday? - Yes, to celebrate...
Happy birthday!
You know that, right?
There aren't any bad people...
- among those who like bread. - Yes.
There aren't any bad people among those who like bread?
Did you buy a lot...
- so you can share with people? - That's right.
- So he had a reason. - Really?
- I wondered why. - Actually,
I was happy while eating it.
But I got even happier...
after meeting people on the way.
Seeing them even happier when I shared the bread,
- I was really happy. - Your happiness was doubled.
He's a happiness ambassador who spreads happiness through bread.
At this rate, you can tour together.
- That'd be really nice. - Seriously.
So when I saw you on TV,
I thought you'd be a good man.
(You're the best.)
Seeing this, the word "pilgrim..."
- actually fits them. - You're right.
- Thank you. - Not at all.
Have a fun trip.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Have a safe trip. - Good luck!
(Thanks to bread, he feels full at heart too.)
It's really fascinating.
All of that is bread, right?
- He's buying bread again? - Hello.
(Smiling broadly)
My goodness. It's the sixth place.
It's the sixth place?
The fact that they sell only one menu...
- There's only one menu on the list. - Exactly.
- It means they have a big pride. - That's right.
They focus on only one menu.
I like salt bread too.
- You like salt bread? - Yes, salt bread is delicious.
- It's simple and light. - That's right.
- You like salty bread. - Yes.
If you like light salt bread,
you can go to M bakery or B bakery, the ones you mentioned.
They have baguette-style salt bread.
But this place has salt bread that tastes like it's fried in butter.
(Realizing)
You don't even have to apply lip balm.
The juice from butter...
It makes your lips glossy.
Just like after we had gimmari.
- Exactly. It's like that. - After eating it...
Gimmari sounds good.
You fill your stomach and keep your lips glossy too.
Thank you.
It's full now.
- Could you give me your autograph? - Sure.
He has young girl fans too.
(A young girl fan approached Bum June, the star.)
Could you write, "Congratulations on graduating?"
- Of course. You graduated? - Yes.
- What's your name? - I'm Lee Ji Yeon.
- I enjoyed your drama. - Really?
Thank you.
They wanted me to sign their yearbook.
(Staring)
Guys, do you like bread?
Yes.
- You can share these. - No, it's okay.
Share them.
Congratulations on graduating.
(Bowing)
Thank you. Goodbye.
(The bread angel shared his bread three times.)
I want to run into you too.
Let's run into each other one day.
Seriously. Let's run into each other.
- Let's go on the bakery pilgrimage. - Yes.
(Happy with both hands full of bread)
(Dropping the bag)
The car will smell like bread.
That's right.
(Getting in the car filled with the smell of bread)
(Gosh, how tiring.)
(Laughing)
(A seat full of bread that makes him smile when he sees it)
It must be really good.
It's so French.
Do you have it for a week if you buy that much?
The bread I got is already gone. I finished them.
Really?
Because I shared it as well.
- Oh, you shared it? - Because there's bread...
for a meal and a dessert,
you can finish them quickly.
There's bread for a meal and a dessert separately in the West.
- That's right. - So it's...
I've never had bread as a dessert.
- I know. - It's like rice.
- That's right. - I consider it a meal.
Then do you not have bread for a dessert after a meal?
- I'd eat something like ice cream. - That's right.
Bread is a bit heavy.
- It makes you full. - But cakes are good.
- You don't eat it? - Cakes aren't that heavy.
- That's right. - Yes. Cakes can be eaten easily.
Don't try to convince me.
I also... I'm sorry. I don't know what I'm saying.
Then...
(Since I got the bread...)
Is that a plate?
- No, a portable table. - That's really convenient.
- That's right. - It's a must in a van.
- That's right. In a van. - Yes, a portable table in a car.
I usually have gukbap on it.
- That's incredible too. - Gukbap?
(Taking it out)
(He took out a paper box instead of gukbap.)
(This must be good.)
(Putting in the bread he specially chose)
Oh, you're arranging them?
It's set.
(The bread from famous bakeries are gathered.)
(Scribbling)
(Writing down in detail how to enjoy it)
Gosh, you're giving them away as a gift?
- You're so sweet. - Well done.
- His handwriting is really nice. - I know.
- It's really pretty. - We said the same thing...
when he wrote something at his sister's bakery.
We said it was handwriting that made our hearts pound.
(That's right.)
(Putting the bread with cold cream cheese in a cold pack)
Look how sensible he is.
I brought them all.
- In case they melt? - Yes.
All set.
(A gift set of famous bakeries' bread is complete.)
(He goes somewhere after packing the bread.)
Bread.
(Driving while humming excitedly)
Gosh.
(The place he arrived with excitement)
(Konkuk University)
- Konkuk University? - You didn't go there...
to have Konkuk Milk, did you?
Konkuk Milk?
To have Konkuk Milk with bread.
(Laughing)
(Looking around to find the milk to have with bread)
(Taking something out)
(Scurrying while relying on the map)
He must be going there to meet someone at Konkuk University.
He looks a bit nervous.
(Nervous)
He must be meeting a professor, seeing his face.
- Right. - It must be a senior he acted with.
- And he became a professor. - Right. I'm 100 percent sure.
- You're 100 percent sure? - For sure.
All right. Let's go in.
(He carefully knocks on the door after hesitating.)
(Exhaling)
(Who did Bum June come to see?)
Hello, sir.
(Bum June came to see someone.)
(Nervous)
(He carefully knocks on the door after hesitating.)
(Exhaling)
Come on in.
- Hello, sir. - Hello.
(Bum June's forever role model, Actor Yoo Ji Tae)
(He was in Korea's iconic movie.)
(His acting skill is always good.)
(Actor with 28 years of experience who's guaranteed to deliver)
(He's famous for his skills as a director as well.)
- Oh, he directs movies too? - Yes.
(He's appointed as a full-time professor at Konkuk University.)
(And 10 years ago)
(Aspiring actor Bum June who was working part-time)
- That's right. Back then... - Oh, my!
I know that content.
(Hi, Bum June.)
- Oh, my. - I was so young, right?
Look at his eyes.
(The meeting that made his dream rock solid)
(Actors live and die by style.)
(Fully recharged good energy from the senior he admires)
(Let's meet each other again in 10 years as fellow actors.)
- That's really cool. - It's so precious.
- I'll wait for you. - It's really precious.
Thank you.
It was a big honor.
(After the 10 years they promised passed...)
(He grew into an actor who won the Best Supporting Actor.)
- You're incredible. - I'll become such an actor.
It mustn't have been the 1st time seeing him within 10 years.
No, I met him next...
at a movie premiere for my movie.
And Ji Tae came.
I said hello to him then...
and asked if he remembered me.
And he said he did.
What a precious encounter.
I also starred in the independent movie he made.
- Gosh. That's so meaningful. - Really?
I always text him after the movie premiere.
- You're a successful fan. - Your paths continue to cross.
That's right.
- It's been long. - Hello.
- You've become more handsome. - Not at all.
I got some bread because you like bread.
Ji Tae also got me bread...
- Oh, my goodness. - because I like bread.
- Take a seat. - Okay.
Thank you.
- You've become more handsome. - Not at all. Thank you.
How have you been?
My recent drama, "Would You Mary Me?" ended.
You got an award for it, right?
(I know. You got an award for it, right?)
- Thank you. - I'm so happy for you.
- Thank you. - You're amazing.
(Honored)
Not at all. I should work harder.
Gosh, I can't believe it.
I know.
The 1st time I met you was in 2016.
- It's been exactly 10 years. - It's been exactly 10 years.
I know.
We said we'd meet each other...
- after ten years, and... - I know.
How can a miracle like this happen?
- It's amazing. - I know.
(Feeling proud of him)
You even won an award. I'm really happy for you.
Not at all. Thank you.
- It's all thanks to you. - Not at all.
You achieved it on your own. It's really amazing.
- You have already... - He must be so proud of you.
I know. He must find him so lovely.
I think the world belongs to those who challenge themselves.
Hi, Bum June.
(The 10 years he challenged himself for his dream)
- I know. I'm choking up. - I know.
- Gosh, congratulations. - You got emotional.
- Gosh. - Goodness. Seriously.
He must be really moved.
Gosh, I'm really happy for you. Goodness.
- I'm sorry. - I'm really proud of you.
- You're amazing. - I'm sorry.
- I'm so proud of you. - Goodness.
(He burst into tears after hearing his senior's compliment.)
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
Gosh, I know how you feel.
I also...
(Clearing his throat)
It's not like I'm pursuing this career because it's guaranteed.
Not at all.
Thanks to the words you said to me,
I got the energy to keep going.
You said actors lived and died by style.
I know. Actors live and die by style.
And that there's no shortcut for anything.
That's right.
To me,
it felt like a promise between us.
I know. I hope it's been helpful.
I always have that in mind.
Actors live and die by style.
And that there's no shortcut for anything.
- Still, Ji Tae... - He's crying again.
- congratulated me too. - Here's why I cried.
Ji Tae congratulated me...
ten years after we met.
The moment I met him for the first time...
- and my debut days... - They must've flashed by.
They flashed by like a movie reel.
Thank you.
(Don't cry, brother.)
Everything flashed by.
(From an aspiring actor to a Best Supporting Actor winner)
So I was...
- That's understandable. - I was grateful.
I cried as soon as I saw you.
(Embarrassed)
This isn't anything much.
(Careful)
Since you're a professor,
I thought you'd use a pen.
- Goodness. - That's the best gift.
I engraved your name on it.
- Gosh, seriously... - Goodness.
I don't know if I deserve this.
Goodness, no. Also...
I...
I don't know if you remember this photo.
Right.
It's ten years ago.
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
It really was ten years ago.
(A photo they took together 10 years ago and a letter)
That's right.
(Moved)
Isn't your movie being released soon?
- Soon? - "The Man..."
That's right. I star in it.
- "The Man Who Lives with the King?" - I act in it.
If there's a movie premiere or stage greeting,
- I'll go there to support you. - Thank you so much.
- I'm looking forward to it. - Right.
We should act together one day as actors.
- I... - You should...
win the Best Actor Award, and we should meet again then.
(Okay)
I saw how you have abs.
It was quite cool.
- But he eats so much bread. - You...
When you filmed the drama, "Vigilante,"
- Right. I buffed up a lot. - you were so...
(Flexing muscles)
It's the kind of body we want for people like us.
Right.
I also want to buff up in my next work.
I don't think you should do that now.
- I should keep my body shape? - Yes, it's better this way.
Bulking up... Is it too soon?
- No, not yet. - Not yet?
- Okay. - You can do it later.
You should star in romantic dramas...
- or romantic comedies. - Right.
After that, you can carefully choose the role.
Right.
You could play a macho role.
That's the dream of men.
Change your image little by little.
(Realistic advice for his junior who's considering different roles)
Today, I brought something. Because I like bread...
Right.
I bought bread from the bakeries famous for their bread.
(Surprised)
- I packed this and that. - Right.
This is a bagel. And this is...
Seriously...
I should really enjoy this bread.
- Since you gave it to me. - Not at all.
Since it's bread you bought me after you became successful,
I should really enjoy it.
- He must be really proud. - I got these for you.
I only chose the delicious ones.
If he sees how you got them,
- he'll be more moved. - I know.
(The bread fills the table in no time.)
That's the bread. That's a bagel. This is Dubai chewy cookie.
- It's popular these days. - I see.
That's really hard to get.
- Let's eat these together. - Okay.
(Cutting)
Dubai chewy cookie.
He's cutting it like he's cutting fish.
He cut it like this.
Because he was recently in a noir film...
- He gives off that vibe. - I thought it was a noir film.
- It didn't feel like... - It feels like a noir film.
He was cutting Dubai chewy cookie.
So this is...
- It's Dubai chewy cookie. - Right.
- Chewy cookie? - Yes, it's popular these days.
(Trying the trending dessert thanks to his junior)
(Having it in a bite without hesitation)
(Thinking)
(Nervous for no reason)
(Exclaiming)
(Smiling broadly)
It's fascinating.
(With a smile, he's out of the noir film.)
I've never tasted anything like this before.
He really enjoyed it.
These days, it's hard to get it,
so people line up around 3 to 4 blocks.
Really?
(He excitedly shares it as Ji Tae likes it.)
You should've said more and told him that it's really hard to get.
- You should've shown off more. - No.
(Taking a big bite of another bread)
It's crunchy.
- He must like bread. - Right.
He's enjoying it more because his junior got it for him.
Right.
- It's delicious. - I'm glad.
Thank you for the bread. It's an honor.
Sure.
You're eating again?
He got it for me.
(Taking a bite carefully and politely)
It's so good.
(Proud)
What's the most fun part of your acting career?
Going to the scene and...
And acting?
- Yes. - That's the most fun part.
Compared to when I think and prepare by myself,
when I go to the scene,
the place is different from what I had in mind.
Right.
The reaction from my co-actor...
is different from what I imagined.
Everything is improvised, and things get added up.
It's really exciting and fun.
- Really? - Yes.
- He listens so well. - I know.
You could encounter a difficulty at the set.
At least you know how precious it is.
- That's right. - That plays a big part.
You already have the quality of a good actor.
You made it possible for me exactly ten years ago.
Not at all.
Not at all. You did it all. You're incredible.
I feel like I got to hear good things again...
and received a lot more 10 years after our 1st encounter.
- I'm really grateful. - How nice.
I want to become a junior...
who can be of support to him one day.
I want to see him as Actor Seo Bum June...
for the rest of my life,
so I should do better.
You're so reliable.
Anyway,
feel the responsibility for the growing expectations.
I hope you'll have the positive responsibility.
All right.
While working,
if you encounter anything difficult, come see me anytime.
Your life has always been precious,
but now, more people are rooting for you.
So I hope you'll take your life more preciously.
Thank you, Ji Tae.
- Come again to have dumplings. - Okay.
My studio is still there.
(Today's Happiness is Nice and Warm Again)
(Next story)
(The Year of the Red Horse)
(Rainbow Running Horses Special)
("Let's Run," "Deep in the Night," "Luxembourg" and more)
(The singer who made all these masterpieces)
(The legend of indie rock with 30 years of experience)
(The band that made the entire nation run)
(The bassist of Crying Nut)
(It's been 20 years since I started living alone.)
(Han Kyung Rok)
(People have a rugged image...)
(when they think of a rocker.)
(I had enough fun when I was young.)
(After that period passed, )
(I developed my own tastes.)
(Right, I was a morning-type rocker.)
It's like blooming brightly.
(Hi, Wilson.)
(You look happy.)
(The godfather rocker's peaceful daily life)
(Putting on a bandana, )
(Captain Rock sets off.)
(Let's do it well!)
(Captain Hongdae patrols the Hongdae area.)
(There are people he knows...)
(here and there.)
(Captain Hongdae has arrived at the square.)
BIBI!
(Here comes BIBI.)
(These days, )
(I've been fangirling over someone.)
(On whom?)
(Fangirling over Crying Nut)
(Me?)
(Filling energy with the people he likes)
(A Colorful Day)
Park Ji Hyeon.
(The winner of the Most Popular Entertainer Award)
(Hot guy, Park Ji Hyeon)
(The hot guy doesn't like cold winter.)
(It'd be bad if it goes cold even for a second.)
(The place he came to with warmth)
(A market filled with hot items)
(This must be warm enough.)
(Satisfied)
(I'm in the 49th batch of Mokpo Technical High School.)
(He's my senior.)
(It's a gift.)
(Warm love poured on the hot guy)
(Popularity is measured...)
(in the marketplace.)
(It's hard to walk past me.)
(He's popular and hot.)
(Why is it so hot?)
(The hot guy's house is even hotter.)
(It's my secret to keep it hot.)
(The hot guy can't cool down.)
(It's nice and warm.)
(Grunting)
(This isn't easy.)
(Spicy tteokbokki that will add more heat)
(It's not spicy.)
(Crying)
Do you want to go to a sauna in the evening?
(How the Hot Guy Survives through Winter)